

# ÖMER F. DOĞAN

Web Developer & Designer

I am a web developer who loves the develop myself and give high performance to my projects. I'm good at MVC structure, angular, react.js, node.js, php and frameworks, responsive design, testing and debugging, UX-UI design and analytical skills from different sectors (Healthcare, Medical, Advertisement, Tourism, E-Commerce and Game). I am open to all kind of research and development projects.

### SKILLS

#### **COMPUTER SKILLS:**

- Angular
- React
- Python
- C#
- PHP
- Node.js
- SQL
- Flutter
- FirebaseHtml
- CSS
- Javascript
- MVC
- React Native
- Adobe PS,AI,XD
- Excel

#### CONTACT

omerfarukdoganweb@gmail.com



+90 541 635 9202

🤎 Pendik / İSTANBUL

## EDUCATION

## Istanbul Gedik University, Istanbul, Turkey

(September 2019-Present)
Computer Programming

## Yakacık Vocational High School, Istanbul, Turkey

(September 2015-June 2019)
Information Technology

# EXPERIENCE

### WEB DEVELOPER & DESIGNER (JUN 2020 - Present)

Pigleb E-Commerce & Software Solutions - Freelance

#### **CHAIRMAN OF COMPUTER SOCIETY (DEC 2019 - Present)**

IEEE Istanbul Gedik University Student Branch

### **SOFTWARE DEVELOPER (JUN 2020 - Present)**

Grapware Digital - Freelance

#### **INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY (JUL 2018 - AUG 2018)**

Aras Kargo - Intern

## IT SUPPORT TECHNICIAN (JUL 2017 - AUG 2017)

Orjin Engineering - Intern

# ACHIEVEMENTS

- Fundamentals of Digital Marketing Google
- · Google Analytics for Beginners Google
- React Solutions Hackerrank
- Web Development Edureka
- Cyber Security 101 IBM

# VOLUNTARY

#### Kızılay

(February 2019-June 2020)

#### **TEMA Foundation**

(February 2019-June 2020)

#### **AFAD**

(September 2020- Present)

## IEEE Member / Volunteer

(May 2019- Present)

# REFERENCES

# Dr. Şenay Kocakoyun Aydoğan

Özyeğin University, Dr.

### Mert Topuz

Kolay Gelsin, Human Resources Manager

#### **Fuat Arslan**

Bluetel, Technical Manager

Contact information of references available upon request.